Aryan Mediratta

About

I am a tech enthusiast who enjoys developing creative solutions with all sorts of technologies.

I'm also proficient in graphic design and animation with kinetic typography using the Adobe Creative Cloud platform.

Certifications

Microsoft Office Specialist (Powerpoint 2016)

Issuer: Microsoft
Identification Code: Gcux-uSwU

MEAN Stack Developer Issuer: Microsoft

DevOps For Developers Issuer: Microsoft

IBM Blockchain Essentials

Issuer: IBM

Hadoop Foundations: Level 1
Issuer: IBM

Big Data Foundations: Level 1 *Issuer: IBM*

Contact

aryan_02@outlook.com https://aryanm.me

Delhi, India



Experience

Vice President Byte Club

May 2018 - Current

I manage the club and handle its functioning. I developed the club's website and the event's promo video.

Programmer Forever EV3

2016 - Current

I program robots using Arduino and Lego Mindstorms EV3. I also enjoy 3D model making and printing. My Robotics team, Forever EV3 has scored an all-India rank of one in RoboCup Junior Rescue 2017 Secondary level.



Education

Bal Bharati Public School, Pitampura High School

Apr 2007 - Current



Projects

Dual-Sensor PID Line Follower Algorithm for LEGO Mindstorms EV3

Dec 2017 - Current

https://github.com/aryan-02/2sensorpid A proportional-integral-derivative line follower algorithm for 2 sensors.

Pi Music Mar 2018

https://github.com/aryan-02/PiMusic
A project I made on Pi Day. It maps the digits of
the decimal expansion of Pi to musical notes and
produces a nice melody while showing the number
that particular tone represents.

µPhone - An iPhone and Pixel Parody

Feb 2017

http://myawesomeproduct.is-best.net
This is a parody website I made for the iPhone 7 and
the Google Pixel



Skills

C++	Javascript	CSS
HTML	PHP	NodeJS
SQL	Express	C#